<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NewsApp</string>
    <string name="news6">X (formerly Twitter) has added a new feature that lets users search for jobs on the microblogging platform. The feature takes on the likes of job search and networking platforms like Microsoft’s LinkedIn, Naukri, Indeed, etc. The new feature comes in line with Elon Musk’s vision of making X the “everything app”. X gets job search feature The new job search feature has been added to the platform via filtres.</string>
    <string name="news1">THE WOODLANDS, TEXAS—The Moon suddenly seems more alive. From 1969 to 1977, seismometers left on the lunar surface by the Apollo astronauts detected thousands of distinctive “moonquakes.” Now, half a century later, a new analysis has cut through the noise in the old data and nearly tripled the number of moonquakes, adding more than 22,000 new quakes to 13,000 previously identified ones.

The finding, presented last week here at the Lunar and Planetary Science Conference, shows “that the Moon may be more seismically and tectonically active today than we had thought,” says Jeffrey Andrews-Hanna, a geophysicist at the University of Arizona unaffiliated with the work, which is in review at the Journal of Geophysical Research. “It is incredible that after 50 years we are still finding new surprises in the data.”

The Apollo missions placed two kinds of seismometers on the surface: ones capable of capturing the 3D motion of long-period seismic waves, and others that recorded more rapid shaking. All of the previously known moonquakes came from the long-period instrument; the short-period data sets contained so much noise, generated by temperature swings between the lunar days and nights, and errors from the radio transmission of the data, that they were indecipherable to 1980s technology. For decades they sat largely untouched. “Literally no one checked all of the short-period data before,”
        says Keisuke Onodera, a seismologist at the University of Tokyo who conducted the new archival analysis.</string>
    <string name="news2">Apple Watch is only compatible with an iPhone but the company said that it spent three years trying to make the Watch compatible with Android. Apple was recently sued by the Department of Justice, claiming it\'s a monopoly.They\'re using the fact that the Apple Watch only works with iPhones as evidence. The argument is that if someone wants to switch from an iPhone to an Android phone, they\'d have to ditch their Apple Watch and buy a new smartwatch that works with Android. This could make switching phones more expensive and inconvenient for users. Apple cited technical issues as the reason behind not being able to make an Apple Watch for Android.</string>
    <string name="news3">Odysseus has exceeded engineers’ expectations during its odyssey on the moon. NASA confirmed that the spindly solar-powered robotic lander, built and operated by the Houston-based private U.S. company Intuitive Machines, has been alive and collecting data since it touched down, and toppled over, on the lunar surface on February 22.

“What a magnificent job that lander did,” said Intuitive Machines CEO Steve Altemus during a NASA news briefing on February 28. “So much data and information and science. It’s just an incredible testament to how robust that little spacecraft is, so we’re really happy with that.”</string>
    <string name="news4">The United Nations General Assembly on Thursday unanimously adopted the first global resolution on artificial intelligence that encourages countries to safeguard human rights, protect personal data, and monitor AI for risks.

The nonbinding resolution, proposed by the United States and co-sponsored by China and over 120 other nations, also advocates the strengthening of privacy policies.

"Today, all 193 members of the United Nations General Assembly have spoken in one voice, and together, chosen to govern artificial intelligence rather than let it govern us," U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations Linda Thomas-Greenfield said.The resolution is the latest in a series of initiatives - few of which carry teeth - by governments around the world to shape AI\'s development, amid fears it could be used to disrupt democratic processes, turbocharge fraud or lead to dramatic job losses, among other harms.

"The improper or malicious design, development, deployment and use of artificial intelligence systems … pose risks that could … undercut the protection, promotion and enjoyment of human rights and fundamental freedoms," the measure says. In November, the U.S., Britain and more than a dozen other countries unveiled the first detailed international agreement on how to keep artificial intelligence safe from rogue actors, pushing for companies to create AI systems that are "secure by design."</string>
</resources>